[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "What is wine",
        "questionId": 1,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.10)",
        "question": "What is the correct formula for fermentation?",
        "answer1": "Sugar + Yeast = Methanol + Carbon Dioxide + Heat",
        "answer2": "Sugar + Yeast = Methanol + Sulfur Dioxide + Heat",
        "answer3": "Sugar + Yeast = Ethanol + Sulfur Dioxide + Heat",
        "answer4": "Sugar + Yeast = Ethanol + Carbon Dioxide + Heat",
        "correctAnswer": "Sugar + Yeast = Ethanol + Carbon Dioxide + Heat"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "What is wine",
        "questionId": 2,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.2)",
        "question": "When yeast comes in contact with sugar, what are the two major waste products?",
        "answer1": "Carbon Dioxide and Sugar",
        "answer2": "Sulfur Dioxide and Ethanol",
        "answer3": "Ethanol and Carbon Dioxide",
        "answer4": "Ethanol and Sugar",
        "correctAnswer": "Ethanol and Carbon Dioxide"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "What is wine",
        "questionId": 3,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.2)",
        "question": "All alcoholic beverages must at some point go through the process of:",
        "answer1": "Lactic Fermentation",
        "answer2": "Alcoholic Fermentation",
        "answer3": "Malolactic Fermentation",
        "answer4": "Malic Fermentation",
        "correctAnswer": "Alcoholic Fermentation"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "What is wine",
        "questionId": 4,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.10)",
        "question": "The specific type of alcohol found in wine, beer, and spirits is:",
        "answer1": "Ethanol",
        "answer2": "Methanol",
        "answer3": "Isopropyl",
        "answer4": "Butanol",
        "correctAnswer": "Ethanol"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "What is wine",
        "questionId": 5,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.2)",
        "question": "The scientific name for the wine grape is:",
        "answer1": "Vitis vinifera",
        "answer2": "Saccharomyces vinifera",
        "answer3": "Saccharomyces cerevisiae",
        "answer4": "Vitis cerevisiae",
        "correctAnswer": "Vitis vinifera"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "What is wine",
        "questionId": 6,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.10)",
        "question": "The scientific name for the yeast used in wine fermentation is:",
        "answer1": "Vitis vinifera",
        "answer2": "Saccharomyces vinifera",
        "answer3": "Saccharomyces cerevisiae",
        "answer4": "Vitis cerevisiae",
        "correctAnswer": "Saccharomyces cerevisiae"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "What is wine",
        "questionId": 7,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.2)",
        "question": "What generates heat during the alcoholic fermentation process?",
        "answer1": "Addition of Ethanol molecules",
        "answer2": "Yeast metabolic activity",
        "answer3": "Addition of Carbon Dioxide molecules",
        "answer4": "Sugar metabolic activity",
        "correctAnswer": "Yeast metabolic activity"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "What is wine",
        "questionId": 8,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.3)",
        "question": "For wine, the two fermentable sugars from grapes and other fruits are:",
        "answer1": "Lactose and Maltose",
        "answer2": "Fructose and Lactose",
        "answer3": "Glucose and Maltose",
        "answer4": "Fructose and Glucose",
        "correctAnswer": "Fructose and Glucose"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "What is wine",
        "questionId": 9,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.3)",
        "question": "Which of the following aspects of Alcoholic Fermentation play a major role in the flavor profiles and characteristics of wine?",
        "answer1": "Ethanol",
        "answer2": "Sugar",
        "answer3": "Heat",
        "answer4": "All of the above",
        "correctAnswer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "What is wine",
        "questionId": 10,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.3)",
        "question": "The warmer a fermentation, the ____ the yeast metabolizes ____.",
        "answer1": "Slower, Sugar",
        "answer2": "Quicker, Carbon Monoxide",
        "answer3": "Quicker, Sugar",
        "answer4": "Slower, Ethanol",
        "correctAnswer": "Quicker, Sugar"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "Wine Grapes",
        "questionId": 1,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.4)",
        "question": "Where is the believed origin of the Vitis vinifera species?",
        "answer1": "Mesopotamia",
        "answer2": "South Africa",
        "answer3": "France",
        "answer4": "Italy",
        "correctAnswer": "Mesopotamia"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "Wine Grapes",
        "questionId": 2,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.4)",
        "question": "Which characteristic makes Vitis vinifera better suited for wine production compared to other species of grapes?",
        "answer1": "High crop yield",
        "answer2": "Pest resistance",
        "answer3": "Stronger fermentation quality",
        "answer4": "None of the above",
        "correctAnswer": "None of the above"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "Wine Grapes",
        "questionId": 3,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.5)",
        "question": "In what order is the evolution of the wine grape (first to last)?",
        "answer1": "Wild Grapes, Domestication, Specialized wine grapes, Selective Breeding",
        "answer2": "Wild Grapes, Specialized wine grapes, Domestication, Selective Breeding",
        "answer3": "Wild Grapes, Selective Breeding, Domestication, Specialized wine grapes",
        "answer4": "Wild Grapes, Domestication, Selective Breeding, Specialized wine grapes",
        "correctAnswer": "Wild Grapes, Domestication, Selective Breeding, Specialized wine grapes"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "Wine Grapes",
        "questionId": 4,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.5)",
        "question": "'When certain vines are selected to produce the next generation of vines due to their characteristics, qualities and agricultural adaptability' is the definition of what stage in wine grape evolution?",
        "answer1": "Domestication",
        "answer2": "Selective Breeding",
        "answer3": "Specialized Wine Grapes",
        "answer4": "Wild Grapes",
        "correctAnswer": "Selective Breeding"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "Wine Grapes",
        "questionId": 5,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.10)",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a specific characteristic of wine grapes?",
        "answer1": "High sugar levels",
        "answer2": "High acid levels",
        "answer3": "Pest resistance",
        "answer4": "Biochemical complexity",
        "correctAnswer": "Pest resistance"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "Wine Grapes",
        "questionId": 6,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.6)",
        "question": "What was the product of the accidental cross-pollination of the Sauvignon Blanc grape and the Cabernet Franc grape?",
        "answer1": "Sauvignon Franc",
        "answer2": "Cabernet Sauvignon",
        "answer3": "Cabernet Blanc",
        "answer4": "Blanc du Franc",
        "correctAnswer": "Cabernet Sauvignon"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "Wine Grapes",
        "questionId": 7,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.6)",
        "question": "Pinot Noir + Cinsaut = ______",
        "answer1": "Cinoir",
        "answer2": "Pinot Saut",
        "answer3": "Pinotage",
        "answer4": "Pinot Blanc",
        "correctAnswer": "Pinotage"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "Wine Grapes",
        "questionId": 8,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.6)",
        "question": "Roughly how many different subspecies of Vitis vinifera are there from the result of selective breeding?",
        "answer1": "3,500",
        "answer2": "1,000,000",
        "answer3": "500,000",
        "answer4": "1",
        "correctAnswer": "3,500"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "Wine Grapes",
        "questionId": 9,
        "reference": "(Gibson, 2010, p.6)",
        "question": "Roughly how many grapes does it take to produce one typical 750ml bottle of dry wine?",
        "answer1": "600 to 800",
        "answer2": "1,500 to 1,700",
        "answer3": "200 to 400",
        "answer4": "1,200 to 1,400",
        "correctAnswer": "600 to 800"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "unit": "Introduction",
        "skill": "Basic 2",
        "questionId": 1,
        "question": "Who are you?",
        "answer1": "Pinot Noir",
        "answer2": "Syrah",
        "answer3": "Merlot",
        "answer4": "Cabernet Sauvignon",
        "correctAnswer": "Syrah"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "unit": "History of Wine",
        "skill": "800s",
        "questionId": 1,
        "question": "What are you doing here?",
        "answer1": "Pinot Noir",
        "answer2": "Syrah",
        "answer3": "Merlot",
        "answer4": "Cabernet Sauvignon",
        "correctAnswer": "Syrah"
    }
]